http://www.developintelligence.com/privacy

Need help finding the right learning solutions? Call Us: 720-445-4360
System Administration
Advanced Java EE Agile Android Angular Ansible Apache Spark AWS Azure C# Chef Communication Data Engineering Docker Git GoLang Google Cloud GraphQL HTML / HTML5 iOS Java JavaScript Jenkins Kotlin Kubernetes Leadership MongoDB Node.js Project Management Puppet Python R React React Native Scala Secure Design Secure Programming Server Administration Swift Terraform
Onboard
For Tech Teams
Reduce initial time to productivity.
Increase employee tenure.
Plug-and-play into HR onboarding and career pathing programs.
Customize for ad-hoc and cohort-based hiring approaches.
Learn more
Upskill
For Tech Teams
Upgrade and round out developer skills.
Tailor to tech stack and specific project.
Help teams, business units, centers of excellence and corporate tech universities.
Learn more
Reskill
For Tech Teams
Offer bootcamps to give employees a running start.
Create immersive and cadenced learning journeys with guaranteed results.
Supplement limited in-house L&D resources with all-inclusive programs to meet specific business goals.
Learn more
Design
For Tech Teams
Uplevel your existing tech learning framework.
Extend HR efforts to provide growth opportunities within the organization.
Prepare your team for an upcoming tech transformation.
Learn more
Privacy Policy
Effective date: January 1, 2019
DevelopIntelligence ("us", "we", or "our") operates the https://www.developintelligence.com website (hereinafter referred to as the "Service").
This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal data when you use our Service and the choices you have associated with that data.
We use your data to provide and improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, the terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, accessible from https://www.developintelligence.com
Definitions
Service
Service is the https://www.developintelligence.com website operated by DevelopIntelligence
Personal Data
Personal Data means data about a living individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).
Usage Data
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).
Cookies
Cookies are small files stored on your device (computer or mobile device).
Information Collection and Use
We collect several different types of information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.
Types of Data Collected
Personal Data
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you ("Personal Data"). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:
Email address First name and last name Phone number Address, State, Province, ZIP/Postal code, City Cookies and Usage Data
Usage Data
We may also collect information on how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer's Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.
Tracking & Cookies Data
We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and we hold certain information.
Cookies are files with a small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking technologies are also used such as beacons, tags and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyse our Service.
You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
Examples of Cookies we use:
Session Cookies. We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
Preference Cookies. We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
Security Cookies. We use Security Cookies for security purposes.
Use of Data
DevelopIntelligence uses the collected data for various purposes:
To provide and maintain our Service
To notify you about changes to our Service
To allow you to participate in interactive features of our Service when you choose to do so
To provide customer support
To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service
To monitor the usage of our Service
To detect, prevent and address technical issues
Transfer of Data
Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ from those of your jurisdiction.
If you are located outside United States and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to United States and process it there.
Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.
DevelopIntelligence will take all the steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organisation or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.
Disclosure of Data
Legal Requirements
DevelopIntelligence may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:
To comply with a legal obligation
To protect and defend the rights or property of DevelopIntelligence
To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
To protect against legal liability
Security of Data
The security of your data is important to us but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.
Service Providers
We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), provide the Service on our behalf, perform Service-related services or assist us in analysing how our Service is used.
These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.
Analytics
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyse the use of our Service.
Clicky
Clicky is a web analytics service. Read the Privacy Policy for Clicky here: https://clicky.com/terms
Behavioral Remarketing
DevelopIntelligence uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimise and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.
AdRoll
AdRoll remarketing service is provided by Semantic Sugar, Inc.
You can opt-out of AdRoll remarketing by visiting this AdRoll Advertising Preferences web page: http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/573?v=1&nt=1&nw=false
For more information on the privacy practices of AdRoll, please visit the AdRoll Privacy Policy web page: http://www.adroll.com/about/privacy
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites that are not operated by us. If you click a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of every site you visit.
We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services.
Children's Privacy
Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").
We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your Child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page.
We will let you know via email and/or a prominent notice on our Service, prior to the change becoming effective and update the "effective date" at the top of this Privacy Policy.
You are advised to review this Privacy Policy periodically for any changes. Changes to this Privacy Policy are effective when they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us:
By email: info@developintelligence.com
Customized Technical Learning Solutions
to Help Attract and Retain Talented Developers
Get In Touch
Talk to one of our Learning Solution Architects today
Let DI help you design solutions to onboard, upskill or reskill your software development organization. Fully customized. 100% guaranteed.
DevelopIntelligence leads technical and software development learning programs for Fortune 500 companies. We provide learning solutions for hundreds of thousands of engineers for over 250 global brands.
Educate learners using experienced practitioners.
Proven customization process is guaranteed.
We're a strategic partner, not just another vendor.
" Best instructor I've ever had. Very knowledgeable and articulate on the subject matter. "
Lewis D
" Rich was a great instructor, he kept me and everyone in this class motivated and wanting to learn more about... "
Anonymous, Verizon Media
“I appreciated the instructor’s technique of writing live code examples rather than using fixed slide decks to present the material.”
VMware
View more
About UsGiving Back
Our Story
Our Team
Testimonials
Work With Us
ResourcesHyperfocus – Free Webinars
2020 Developer Learning Report
Case Study :: Cloud Transformation
Case Study :: Retain Tech Talent
Case Study :: Professional Development
Whitepaper :: Self-Paced vs. ILT
Whitepaper :: Digital Transformations for L&D Leaders
Some Popular TechnologiesAll Courses (IT Training)
Android Training
Angular Training
Git Training
HTML Training
Java Training
JavaScript Training
AWS Training
Kubernetes Training
React Training
Docker Training
Jenkins Training
Thank you for everyone who joined us this past year to hear about our proven methods of attracting and retaining tech talent.
FacebookTwitterLinkedin
Boulder, Colorado Headquarters: 980 W. Dillon Road, Louisville, CO 80027
877-629-5631, 720-445-4360
© 2013 - 2020 DevelopIntelligence LLC - Privacy Policy
AboutBlogSolutionsWhy UsContactCourses
OnboardUpskillReskillDesign
Giving Back
Our Story
Our Team
Testimonials
System Admin
.NETAdvanced Java EEApache MavenC#C++CassandraCore JavaGitGoLangGoogle CloudGrailsGroovyHibernateJavaJavaScriptJMSJPAKotlinLuceneMongoDBNode.jsNoSQLPerlPHPPythonRPARuby on RailsRustScalaSolrSpring.ioSQLStrutsTestingUMLWeb DevelopmentWebLogic ApacheApache SparkAzureCassandraData EngineeringData VisualizationExcelGemfireGoLangGoogle CloudGrafanaHadoopIncortaKafkaMongoDBNoSQLPythonRScalaSearchSnowflakeSolrTableau
AnsibleAWSAzureChefCloud NativeDockerGoogle CloudHerokuKubernetesOpenStackPuppetSaltStackSpinnaker AgileAnsibleAzureBitbucketChefCI/CDDevelopment ToolsDockerElkGitGoogle CloudJenkinsJIRAKubernetesMonitoring & LoggingNexusPuppetPythonSaltStackSpinnakerSplunkSRETerraformVagrantZabbix
AjaxAngularCSSD3ElmGraphQLHTML / HTML5JasmineJavaScriptjQueryNode.jsPHPReactRelay ModernRuby on RailsRustSeleniumVue.jsWeb DesignWeb Development AIApache SparkAzureCUDAData ScienceDeep LearningGoogle CloudKafkaNLPPythonPyTorchRSageMakerTableau
AndroidFlutterHTML / HTML5iOSKotlinReact NativeSwiftWeb Development AgileDesign PatternsDevelopment ToolsITILJIRAOOADRUPSoftware ArchitectureTestingUI/UXUML Apache HTTPDAWSAzureGlassfishGoogle CloudJBossLinuxMySQLServer AdministrationSubversion
Scroll to top
Get In Touch
Get Free Assessment
Let's review your current tech training programs and we'll help you baseline your success against some of our big industry partners. In this 30-minute meeting, we'll share our data/insights on what's working and what's not.
Or
Get In Touch Directly
720-445-4360info@developintelligence.com
The Good and Bad on Training Developers
Training Journal sat down with our CEO for his thoughts on what’s working, and what’s not working.
https://s3-us-east-2.amazonaws.com/ditrainingco/wp-content/uploads/2020/01/28083328/TJtalks_-Kelby-Zorgdrager-on-training-developers.mp3
